GUSTAV LORENTZEN

Tel: 0045-30620087 gustavlorentzen7@gmai l.com Soenderengen 24a 2870 Dyssegaard

PROFILE

Looking for work in a ski school with challenging task and good company with friendly people.

I am a 21-years-old young man who finished his high school exam at Aurehøj Gymnasium last summer, and am currently on my second gap year. I speak fluent English, understand a bit of French and speak native Danish.

I love skiing and am very motivated to work for a ski school. Since I was a little boy, I have been skiing with my family at least once a year, often for a week at a time. I probably have about 25 weeks on skis spread over the last 18 years of my life. I took the BASI 2 exam here in October, and passed theory, teaching practice and the free run, but unfortunately couldn't pass the whole course. I therefore hope to take the BASI 2 exam as soon as possible.

By hiring me, you will get an employee who is hardworking, keeps a cool head in stressful situations and who is loyal to his fellow people. I am a rational, practical thinker, positive and good at listening. My commitment is great, and in specific task I am sharp and analytical.

I think I could be a ressorce at your workplace, and therefore hope to be considered for the job as ski instructor at your ski school.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2018 - 2019 Cashier

Kvickly budding, Søborg

2021 - Present Web Developer

Itavis, Klampenborg

EDUCATION

2018 - 2021 High School

Aurehøj Gymnasium

2021 Ski Instructor

BSI 1 (BASI 1), The Danish Ski Shcool

2021 - 2022 Programming

Html, CSS & Javascript, The Odin Project